{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722627631","data":{"timestamp":" 947722627631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722639856","data":{"timestamp":" 947722639856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722640078","data":{"timestamp":" 947722640078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722641042","data":{"timestamp":" 947722641041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722642315","data":{"timestamp":" 947722642315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722645186","data":{"timestamp":" 947722645186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722646028","data":{"timestamp":" 947722646028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722646341","data":{"timestamp":" 947722646341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722647574","data":{"timestamp":" 947722647574"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722651056","data":{"timestamp":" 947722651056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722652039","data":{"timestamp":" 947722652039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722652292","data":{"timestamp":" 947722652292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722653236","data":{"timestamp":" 947722653236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722656061","data":{"timestamp":" 947722656061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722657093","data":{"timestamp":" 947722657093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722657566","data":{"timestamp":" 947722657566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722662079","data":{"timestamp":" 947722662078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722662138","data":{"timestamp":" 947722662138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 89ada361-a5d4-48dd-bb7e-b637836b2c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722678484","data":{"timestamp":" 947722678484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIGOE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722680655","data":{"timestamp":" 947722680655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722682840","data":{"timestamp":" 947722682840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722684962","data":{"timestamp":" 947722684962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722687022","data":{"timestamp":" 947722687022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722689755","data":{"timestamp":" 947722689755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722691976","data":{"timestamp":" 947722691976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722695578","data":{"timestamp":" 947722695578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722697730","data":{"timestamp":" 947722697730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722699244","data":{"timestamp":" 947722699244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722699619","data":{"timestamp":" 947722699619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722702248","data":{"timestamp":" 947722702248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722704445","data":{"timestamp":" 947722704445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722708081","data":{"timestamp":" 947722708081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722710856","data":{"timestamp":" 947722710856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722713185","data":{"timestamp":" 947722713185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722715284","data":{"timestamp":" 947722715284"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722715576","data":{"timestamp":" 947722715576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722717489","data":{"timestamp":" 947722717489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722719551","data":{"timestamp":" 947722719551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722722315","data":{"timestamp":" 947722722314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722725134","data":{"timestamp":" 947722725133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722727996","data":{"timestamp":" 947722727996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722731181","data":{"timestamp":" 947722731180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722734287","data":{"timestamp":" 947722734286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722736127","data":{"timestamp":" 947722736127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722738249","data":{"timestamp":" 947722738249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722740271","data":{"timestamp":" 947722740271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722742826","data":{"timestamp":" 947722742826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722747747","data":{"timestamp":" 947722747747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722750578","data":{"timestamp":" 947722750578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722753219","data":{"timestamp":" 947722753219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722755150","data":{"timestamp":" 947722755149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722757570","data":{"timestamp":" 947722757570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANDUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722759860","data":{"timestamp":" 947722759860"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722762862","data":{"timestamp":" 947722762862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722765379","data":{"timestamp":" 947722765379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722767882","data":{"timestamp":" 947722767882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DALILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722773518","data":{"timestamp":" 947722773518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722775849","data":{"timestamp":" 947722775849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722779375","data":{"timestamp":" 947722779375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta katika dari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722783392","data":{"timestamp":" 947722783392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta katika dari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722787835","data":{"timestamp":" 947722787835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta katika dari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722789626","data":{"timestamp":" 947722789626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANGALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722791414","data":{"timestamp":" 947722791414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722793254","data":{"timestamp":" 947722793253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722802225","data":{"timestamp":" 947722802225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722806223","data":{"timestamp":" 947722806222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKAANGALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722813019","data":{"timestamp":" 947722813018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722815045","data":{"timestamp":" 947722815045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722815750","data":{"timestamp":" 947722815750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722817745","data":{"timestamp":" 947722817744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722820386","data":{"timestamp":" 947722820386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722823977","data":{"timestamp":" 947722823977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722827200","data":{"timestamp":" 947722827200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" START_SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722829122","data":{"timestamp":" 947722829121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722850785","data":{"timestamp":" 947722850785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722850858","data":{"timestamp":" 947722850858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 2cd4f8a6-e9fb-455e-8b25-b04776a75d81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722862327","data":{"timestamp":" 947722862326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIGOE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722863699","data":{"timestamp":" 947722863698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722865764","data":{"timestamp":" 947722865764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722868523","data":{"timestamp":" 947722868523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" START_CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722870836","data":{"timestamp":" 947722870835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" KIMEPOTEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722872096","data":{"timestamp":" 947722872096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722873071","data":{"timestamp":" 947722873070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZEA"," userResponse":" KIGOE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722874477","data":{"timestamp":" 947722874477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZEA"," userResponse":" KIGOE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722876216","data":{"timestamp":" 947722876216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722877181","data":{"timestamp":" 947722877180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TENISI"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722882101","data":{"timestamp":" 947722882101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENISI"," userResponse":" TENISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722884925","data":{"timestamp":" 947722884925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" KIGOE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722887675","data":{"timestamp":" 947722887674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722890253","data":{"timestamp":" 947722890253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722894779","data":{"timestamp":" 947722894779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722896233","data":{"timestamp":" 947722896232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947722896297","data":{"timestamp":" 947722896297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_031646"," gameId":" 7473997c-ad31-4697-9674-e9da70eaaa5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}